Guide to the War Poster Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- World War I, 1914-1918; Series I
  - Lafon Allen Collection
    - Great Britain
      - Be Schikkingen Aangaande de Uitdeeling Van Suiker, 1917 December; AGB0948; 20x30 inches (Box 96)
      - League of National Safety. Food Economy, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0949; 20x30 inches (Box 96)
      - Food Economy. The Nation's SOS, Save or Starve. Join the League, 1917 December; AGB0950; 20x30 inches (Box 96)
      - Food. Buy It with Thought, Cook it with Care, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0951; 20x30 inches (Box 96)
      - A Message, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0952; 10x15 inches (Box 96)
      - Think! For Every 100,000 Tons of Wheat Saved by Economy, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0953; 20x30 inches (Box 96)
      - If One 600,000 Grain Ship is Sunk, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0954; 10x15 inches (Box 96)
      - Ministry of Food. Tea Registration, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0955; 17x22 inches (Box 96)
      - Ministry of Food. Table of Equivalent Weights of Meat Other, 1918 March 25; AGB0956; 20x30 inches (Box 96)
      - Ministry of Food. Table of Equivalent of Meat, Poultry and Game., 1918 March 25; AGB0957; 20x30 inches (Box 96)
      - Ministry of Food. Meat Ration Order 1918. Notice to the Public, 1918 March; AGB0958; 20x30 inches (Box 96)
      - To the Men and Women of Britain, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0959; 17x21 inches (Box 96)
      - Ministry of Food. Ration. How to Use Your Food Cards, 1918 February; AGB0960; 20x30 inches (Box 96)
      - Uniform Scale of Retail Prices of Meat, 1918 March 1; AGB0961; 23x36 inches (Box 97)
      - I Risked My Life to Bring You Food, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0962; 08x11 inches (Box 97)
      - Ministry of Labor. The Ministry of Food Requires Girls, 1917 November; AGB0963; 21x32 inches (Box 97)
      - Ministry of Food. Meat Rationing Order 1918, 1918 May 6; AGB0964; 09x13 inches (Box 97)
      - Ministry of Food. A Rationing Order 1918. Directions for Retailers, 1918 July; AGB0965; 10x15 inches (Box 97)
      - Ministry of Food. A Rationing Order, 1918. Directions for General, 1918 July; AGB0966; 10x15 inches (Box 97)
      - Ministry of Food Rationing Order 1918, 1918 July; AGB0967; 20x30 inches (Box 97)
      - Ministry of Food. Food Control Committee's Distribution Scheme, 1918 March; AGB0968; 09x14 inches (Box 97)
      - Ministry of Food. The Cereals (restriction) Order 1918, 1918 August; AGB0969; 20x30 inches (Box 97)
      - Uniform Scale of Maximum Retail Prices for Meat., 1918 September 22; AGB0970; 23x35 inches (Box 97)
      - Uniform Scale of Maximum Retail Prices for Meat. [Yiddish], 1918 September 22; AGB0971; 23x35 inches (Box 97)
      - Uniform Scale of Maximum Retail Prices for Offall, 1918 September 22; AGB0972; 20x30 inches (Box 97)
      - Ministry of Food. Fish Prices Order No. 3; October 21, 1918., 1918 October; AGB0973; 30x40 inches (Box 97)
      - Pork, 1918 December; AGB0974; 12x17 inches (Box 97)
      - Pork, 1918 December; AGB0975; 10x13 inches (Box 97)
      - Ministry of Food. Priority for Dairy Cows in Cattle Feeding, 1918 February; AGB0976; 13x17 inches (Box 97)
      - Ministry of Food. Retail Maximum Prices of Some of the Main, 1918 May; AGB0977; 30x22 inches (Box 97)
      - Ministry of Food. Notice in Shops (Ireland) Order No. 400, 1918 June; AGB0978; 15x22 inches (Box 97)
      - Food Production in 1918, 1918 February; AGB0979; 10x15 inches (Box 97)
      - Grow More Food, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0980; 20x30 inches (Box 97)
      - Grow More Food, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0981; 15x20 inches (Box 98)
      - Ministry of Food. The Rationing Order, 1918, 1918 July; AGB0982; 10x15 inches (Box 98)
      - Ministry of Food. The Rationing Order, 1918, 1918 July; AGB0983; 10x15 inches (Box 98)
      - Ministry of Food. Notice. Slaughter Permits for Cattle and Sheep., 1918 July 15; AGB0984; 20x30 inches (Box 98)
      - Rations! Have You Got Your Food Cards?, 1918 February; AGB0985; 30x10 inches (Box 98)
      - Ministry of Food. Rationing Forms, 1918 August; AGB0986; 15x20 inches (Box 98)
      - Uniform Scale of Maximum Retail Prices for Meat, Scotland, 1918 August 22; AGB0987; 22x35 inches (Box 98)
      - Unknown Rationing Order, 1918. Table of Equivalent Weights of Meat, 1918 September; AGB0988; 20x30 inches (Box 98)
      - Uniform Scale of Maximum Retail Prices for Meat, England and Wales, 1918 September 22; AGB0989; 23x35 inches (Box 98)
      - Uniform Scale of Maximum Retail Prices for Meat, England and Wales, 1918 September 22; AGB0990; 23x35 inches (Box 98)
      - The Meat (maximum prices) Order, 1917, 1918 September 22; AGB0991; 15x20 inches (Box 98)
      - Ministry of Food. Pig (Sales) Order, 1918, 1918 September; AGB0992; 20x30 inches (Box 98)
      - Defense of the Realm. Ministry of Food. Selling New Bread, 1918 October; AGB0993; 19x12 inches (Box 98)
      - Eat Less Bread., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0994; 29x10 inches (Box 98)
      - Household Coal Distribution Order, 1917. Notice to Consumers, 1917 September; AGB0995; 25x40 inches (Box 99)
      - Bones and Fat Provide Glycerine for Making Explosives, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0996; 11x16 inches (Box 99)
      - Bones and Fat Provide Glycerine for Making Explosives, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0997; 20x30 inches (Box 99)
      - The Coal You Are Going without Is Forging the Key to Victory., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0998; 20x30 inches (Box 99)
      - The Coal You Are Going without Is Forging the Key to Victory., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0999; 25x30 inches (Box 99)
      - The Coal You Are Going without Is Forging the Key to Victory., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1000; 40x58 inches (Box 99)
      - The Coal You Are Going without Is Forging the Key to Victory., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1001; 60x120 inches (Box 99)
      - National Salvage. Save Everything, Waste Nothing, 1918 April; AGB1002; 17x22 inches (Box 99)
      - National Salvage Council. We Are Asked to Collect All Fruit, 1918 July; AGB1003; 10x15 inches (Box 99)
      - Burn Your Cinders and Save Coal., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1004; 20x30 inches (Box 99)
      - Save Your Bit., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1005; 20x30 inches (Box 99)
      - Fewer Hot Baths and Save Coal., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1006; 20x30 inches (Box 99)
      - Go To Bed Early and Save Coal., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1007; 20x30 inches (Box 99)
      - The Greatest Economy Is Necessary with Coal, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1008; 20x30 inches (Box 99)
      - Coal. If, for Everyone in the Kingdom a Piece of Coal As Big, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1009; 20x30 inches (Box 99)
      - Coal. If, for Everyone in the Kingdom a Piece of Coal As Big, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1010; 40x60 inches (Box 99)
      - Carry Home Your Own Parcels. Motors, Petrol and Horses, 1918 January; AGB1011; 10x15 inches (Box 99)
      - Coal Saving a National Duty. If for Each Man, Woman and Child, 1918 May; AGB1012; 06x10 inches (Box 99)
      - Cut More Turf. Coal Will Be Short, 1918 May; AGB1013; 18x22 inches (Box 99)
      - Coal Saving a National Duty, 1918 May; AGB1014; 20x30 inches (Box 99)
      - Coal Shortage. Urgent Need for Economy, 1918 June; AGB1015; 20x30 inches (Box 99)
      - Defense of the Realm Regulations. Census of Horses Ordered, 1918, 1918 October; AGB1016; 13x17 inches (Box 99)
      - National Service. If You Cannot Fight for Your Country, Work, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1017; 29x12 inches (Box 100)
      - National Service. Defend Your Island from the Grimmest Menace, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1018; 30x40 inches (Box 100)
      - National Service. Germany Means to Starve Us Out, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1019; 78x118 inches (Box 100)
      - National Service. If You Cannot Fight for Your Country, Work, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1020; 24x18 inches (Box 100)
      - National Service. Germany Means to Starve Us Out, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1021; 08x12 inches (Box 100)
      - National Service. Germany Means to Starve Us Out, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1022; 20x30 inches (Box 100)
      - National Service. Enroll Today and Release a Fit Man for the Front., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1023; 80x30 inches (Box 100)
      - National Service. Enroll Today and Back Up the Men in the Trenches., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1024; 29x12 inches (Box 100)
      - Help to Defeat the Grimmest Menace that Ever Threatened, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1025; 19x09 inches (Box 100)
      - Back Up the Boys in the Trenches, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1026; 19x15 inches (Box 100)
      - Victory at the Front Depends upon Work Done at Home, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1027; 19x15 inches (Box 100)
      - Have You Enrolled for National Service, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1028; 20x30 inches (Box 100)
      - National Service. Women's Land Army. God Speed the Plow, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1029; 20x30 inches (Box 100)
      - 10,000 Women Wanted for Farm Work, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1030; 30x40 inches (Box 100)
      - 10,000 Women Wanted for Farm Work, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1031; 15x20 inches (Box 101)
      - 10,000 Women Wanted for Farm Work, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1032; 20x30 inches (Box 101)
      - 10,000 Women Wanted for Farm Work, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1033; 15x20 inches (Box 101)
      - 10,000 Women Wanted for Farm Work, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1034; 10x15 inches (Box 101)
      - Women Clerks Wanted at once for Service in France, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1035; 20x30 inches (Box 101)
      - Hands Wanted for National Service, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1036; 25x38 inches (Box 101)
      - Who Follows? The Nation Is Fighting for Its Life., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1037; 20x30 inches (Box 101)
      - Who Follows? The Nation Is Fighting for Its Life. All Men Who, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1038; 12x20 inches (Box 101)
      - To National Service Department, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1039; 58x21 inches (Box 101)
      - Farmers, Are You Needing Labor for the Land? If So, Employ Women, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1040; 20x30 inches (Box 101)
      - Women's Land Army., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1041; 20x30 inches (Box 101)
      - The Church Army Huts, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1042; 20x30 inches (Box 102)
      - London Hut Week, May 19-26, AGB1043; 20x30 inches (Box 102)
      - The Y.M.C.A. Dug-Out in France., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1044; 40x30 inches (Box 102)
      - 3 A.M. in a London Station Hut., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1045; 40x30 inches (Box 102)
      - The Y.M.C.A. Motor-Kitchen in France., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1046; 40x30 inches (Box 102)
      - The Y.M.C.A. Service for Relatives of Dangerously Wounded., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1047; 40x30 inches (Box 102)
      - A British Training Camp., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1048; 30x20 inches (Box 102)
      - A Y.M.C.A. Dug-Out in France., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1049; 30x20 inches (Box 102)
      - The King's Call to the Empire. Day of National Prayer, 1918 January 6; AGB1050; 20x30 inches (Box 102)
      - The Salvation Army and its War Work., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1051; 20x30 inches (Box 102)
      - The Salvation Army. War Flag Day, June 9th., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1052; 20x30 inches (Box 102)
      - United National Prayer for the War, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1053; 20x30 inches (Box 102)
      - Admiral Sir D. Beatty on the Duration of the War, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1054; 30x10 inches (Box 102)
      - Admiral Sir D. Beatty on the Duration of the War, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1055; 40x60 inches (Box 102)
      - The Salvation Army. War Flag Day, Saturday, June 9th., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1056; 30x40 inches (Box 102)
      - Church Army War Work, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1057; 20x30 inches (Box 102)
      - Salvation Army Soldiers' Hostels, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1058; 20x30 inches (Box 102)
      - Church Army War Work Sale Will Take Place in the Central, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1059; 15x20 inches (Box 102)
      - The Church Army in Palestine, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1060; 20x30 inches (Box 102)
      - Church Army Soldiers' Hostels, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1061; 20x30 inches (Box 102)
      - Flag Day. Church Army June 4th, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1062; 30x40 inches (Box 102)
        Artist: Fitzsimmons, D.D.. Place of Publication: Great Britain.
      - Y.M.C.A. Thirty Centers in East Africa., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1063; 11x15 inches (Box 102)
      - Y.M.C.A. Fifty-eight Centers in Egypt and Palestine., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1064; 11x15 inches (Box 102)
      - Twenty-eight Centers in Salonica., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1065; 11x15 inches (Box 102)
      - Y.M.C.A. Fifteen Hundred Centers in the Home Campus., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1066; 11x15 inches (Box 102)
      - Y.M.C.A. Forty-seven Centers in Mesopotamia., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1067; 11x15 inches (Box 102)
      - Y.M.C.A. Fifty Centers in Italy and Mediterranean., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1068; 11x15 inches (Box 102)
      - Y.M.C.A. Forty-five Centers in India., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1069; 11x15 inches (Box 102)
      - Y.M.C.A. Huts and Hostels in Ports and Naval Bases., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1070; 11x15 inches (Box 102)
      - Y.M.C.A. One Hundred and Fifty Centers in Conquested Munition, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1071; 11x15 inches (Box 102)
      - Y.M.C.A. Five Hundred Centers in France and Flanders., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1072; 11x15 inches (Box 102)
      - Y.M.C.A. Book Posters., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1073; 10x13 inches (Box 102)
      - Hut Day, Friday, May 10th., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1074; 20x30 inches (Box 102)
      - Thursday, June 6th, 1918 Flag Day Demonstration Representing, 1918 June 6; AGB1075; 20x30 inches (Box 102)
      - War Flag Day, Friday-Saturday, June 7-8, AGB1076; 20x30 inches (Box 103)
      - War Flag Day, Friday-Saturday, June 7-8, AGB1077; 30x40 inches (Box 103)
      - Church vs. Australians at Lord's Saturday July 6th, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1078; 20x30 inches (Box 103)
      - Y.M.C.A. Hostels, Clubs, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1079; 22x35 inches (Box 103)
      - War Prayer Meeting, Mansio House, Thursdays, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1080; 20x30 inches (Box 103)
      - Prayer for Victory. The Noon Watch. Will You Join Those Who, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1081; 20x30 inches (Box 103)
      - General Sir William Robertson, Prayer for Victory, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1082; 20x30 inches (Box 103)
      - Will You Pray about the War?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1083; 12x15 inches (Box 103)
      - Marked Out by Line of White Tape, The Road from Hell Leads, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1084; 20x30 inches (Box 103)
      - Admiral Sir D. Beatty on the Duration of the War, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1085; 30x10 inches (Box 103)
      - In the War Zone. Tribute from Field Marshall Sir Douglas Haig, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1086; 30x40 inches (Box 103)
      - Save All Waste Paper, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1087; 20x30 inches (Box 103)
      - Church Army Soldier's Hostels Open Day and Night, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1088; 20x30 inches (Box 103)
      - Church Army Hostels and Rest Houses for Service Men, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1089; 20x30 inches (Box 103)
      - In Aid of Camberwell Church Army Hut Fund, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1090; 20x30 inches (Box 103)
      - Don't Pity a Disabled Man; Find Him a Job., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1091; 20x30 inches (Box 103)
        Artist: Abbey, Edwin Austin. Place of Publication: Great Britain.
      - Church Army Hotel and Rest Houses for Service Men, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1092; 30x30 inches (Box 103)
      - Discharged Sailors and Soldiers; Special Employment Exchange, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1093; 20x30 inches (Box 104)
      - No Holidays., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1094; 30x40 inches (Box 104)
      - Postponement of Holidays, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1095; 20x30 inches (Box 104)
      - German Trenches on the West Front: Before Bombardment, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1096; 30x40 inches (Box 104)
      - After Bombardment: Munition Workers, See the Effect of Your Work, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1097; 30x40 inches (Box 104)
      - Mars Appeals to Vulcan., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1098; 20x30 inches (Box 104)
      - Ministry of Munitions of War., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1099; 22x32 inches (Box 104)
      - Warning: Employment of Men Liable to Military Service, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1100; 20x30 inches (Box 104)
      - Soldiers All, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1101; 20x30 inches (Box 104)
      - London Opera House: Anniversary of the Battle of Jutland, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1102; 20x30 inches (Box 104)
      - Soldiers and Sailors, Come to the New Recreation Club, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1103; 18x23 inches (Box 104)
      - Postpone Your Holiday. An Appeal to the Nation by Sir Douglas, 1916 July; AGB1104; 30x40 inches (Box 104)
      - The Zeppelin Raids. The Vow of Vengeance, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1105; 20x30 inches (Box 104)
      - Do Your Duty to Our Boys as They Are Doing Theirs to You, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1106; 30x20 inches (Box 104)
      - The Men Behind the Man Behind the Gun., 1917 December; AGB1107; 20x30 inches (Box 104)
      - Thank God and the Sailors for my Good Breakfast., 1917 December; AGB1108; 20x30 inches (Box 104)
      - Disabled Sailors and Soldiers. What Every Man Should Know, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1109; 30x04 inches (Box 104)
      - Sailors or Soldiers Disabled in the War Should Report at Once, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1110; 10x14 inches (Box 104)
      - Imperial Defense Union. Germany's Desire for World Power, 1918 June; AGB1111; 20x30 inches (Box 104)
      - Liberte, Egalite, Fraternite. Ils ne passeront pas., 1918 July; AGB1112; 20x30 inches (Box 104)
      - To France., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1113; 20x30 inches (Box 104)
      - First Grand Exhibition of British Battle Photographs in Color, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1114; 20x30 inches (Box 104)
      - Ministry of Labor, Employment Dept. Leaflets of Interest, 1918 August; AGB1115; 13x17 inches (Box 104)
      - L. & N.W. Reilly's Roll of Honour, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1116; 60x40 inches (Box 104)
        Artist: Furniss, Harry. Place of Publication: Great Britain.
      - To Skilled Workmen. Give Your Strength and Your Skill to Your, 1915 June; AGB1117; 20x30 inches (Box 104)
      - From War to Peace. Employers Notify Your Vacancies at Once, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1118; 19x29 inches (Box 104)
      - Belgium, 1914., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB1119; 40x60 inches (Box 104)
      - Recruiting Offices, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGBU0009 (Box 105)
      - Recruiting Office, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGBU0010 (Box 105)
      - Lamp Day, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGBU0011 (Box 105)
      - Lamp Day, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGBU0012 (Box 105)
      - Army Reserve, 1916 January 29; AGBU0007 (Box 105)
      - Army Reserve, 1916 February 10; AGBU0007 (Box 105)
      - Army Reserve, 1916 February 16; AGBU0007 (Box 105)
      - Army Reserve, 1916 February 16; AGBU0007 (Box 105)
      - Army Reserve, 1916 March 7; AGBU0007 (Box 105)
      - Army Reserve, 1916 March 7; AGBU0007 (Box 105)
      - Army Reserve, 1916 April 29; AGBU0007 (Box 105)
      - Army Reserve, 1916 June 3; AGBU0007 (Box 105)
      - Don't, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGBU0008 (Box 105)
      - Globe Theatre: Matinee in the Aid of the British Women's Hospital Appeal for The Nation's Fund for Nurses, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGBU0013 (Box 105)
      - War! Please Help the Horses: The Blue Cross Fund, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGBU0006 (Box 105)
      - Army Reserve, 1916 September 7; AGBU0007 (Box 105)
        Artist: Unknown. Place of Publication: Great Britain. Appears to be 2 posters on 1 piece of paper.
      - Army Reserve, 1916 May 13; AGBU0007 (Box 105)
      - Army Reserve, 1916 April 10; AGBU0007 (Box 105)
      - Army Reserve, 1916 February 26; AGBU0007 (Box 105)
      - Army Reserve, 1916 February 16; AGBU0007 (Box 105)
      - Army Reserve, 1915 December 20; AGBU0007 (Box 105)
      - Army Reserve, 1916 January 8; AGBU0007 (Box 105)
      - Join in the Woolwich Great Recruiting Rally, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGBU0002 (Box 105)
      - Khaki Magazine and Cabled News Sheet, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGBU0003 (Box 105)
      - Diagrams of British and German Airships, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGBU0004 (Box 105)
      - Grand Military Display by the Coldstream Guards, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGBU0005 (Box 105)
      - National Savings, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGBU0001 (Box 105)
      - No. 73, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 105)
        Artist: Unknown. Place of Publication: Unknown. Depiction of tank.
      - No. 78, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 105)
        Artist: Unknown. Place of Publication: Unknown. Depiction of planes.
      - No. 79, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 105)
        Artist: Unknown. Place of Publication: Unknown. Depiction of artillery.
    - Germany
      - Avis au Maire-Odre de Requisition-La Commune de Luneville, 1914 August 29; AGE0001; 12x17 inches (Box 106)
        Artist: Unknown. Place of Publication: Germany.
      - Defense d'Arracher. Autorite Militaire Allemande, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGE0002; 12x17 inches (Box 106)
      - Toutes les autorites du Gouvernement, 1914 September 4; AGE0003; 20x26 inches (Box 106)
      - M_, rue_,no._ Composition de la Famille, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGE0004; 11x09 inches (Box 106)
      - Il est strictement defendu aux habitants, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGE0005; 16x12 inches (Box 106)
      - A la Population de Luneville, 1914 August 28; AGE0006; 19x32 inches (Box 106)
      - La Population de la Ville est, des ce jour, 1914 September 10; AGE0007; 16x24 inches (Box 106)
      - Ordre a La Population Liegeoise, 1914 August 22; AGE0008; 24x16 inches (Box 106)
      - Avis a la Population. Le 23 Aout 1914, des habitants, 1914 September 3; AGE0009; 12x16 inches (Box 106)
      - du Commandant militarire Allemand de Lille, 1916 April; AGE0010; 22x16 inches (Box 106)
      - Avis-Tous les inhabitants de la maison. doivent se preparer, 1916 April; AGE0011; 16x22 inches (Box 106)
      - Aux Habitants de la Belgique-Le Marechal Von der Goltz, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGE0012; 12x17 inches (Box 106)
      - Aux Habitants de la Belgique-Le Marechal Von der Goltz, 1914 September 18; AGE0013; 15x22 inches (Box 106)
      - Bekanntmachung - Seine Majestat der Kaiser und konig, 1914 August 1; AGE0014; 22x32 inches (Box 106)
      - Au Peuple Belge. C'est a mon plus grand regret que les troupes, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGE0015; 24x34 inches (Box 106)
      - AVIS - Les personnes mentionnees ci-dessous ont ete condamnees, 1915 September 22; AGE0016; 24x34 inches (Box 106)
      - Avis Relatif au Travail Volontaire Exige des Civile, 1916 November 15; AGE0017; 16x24 inches (Box 106)
      - Aux Habitants de la Ville de Lille, 1914 October 14; AGE0018; 18x26 inches (Box 106)
      - Francais! Vos aviateurs, au moyen de lancement de bombes, 1916 July 26; AGE0019; 13x17 inches (Box 106)
      - Proclamation. Le Tribunal du Conseil de Guerre Imperial, 1915 October 12; AGE0020; 24x34 inches (Box 106)
      - Avis - a la Population-Afin d'assurer suffisamment la securite, 1914 September 12; AGE0021; 20x26 inches (Box 106)
      - Avis a la Population-Afin d'assurer suffisamment, 1914 September 12; AGE0022; 22x17 inches (Box 106)
      - Proclamation aux Habitants de Saint-Die, 1914 August 27; AGE0023; 18x22 inches (Box 106)
      - AVIS - Les nombreux actes d'hostilite commis par les habitants, 1914 August 28; AGE0024; 17x24 inches (Box 106)
      - An das deutsche Volk, 1914 August 6; AGE0025; 20x29 inches (Box 106)